

CONTACT ME AT

piotrpospiech00@gmail.com

piotrpospiech.com



+45 91 95 31 33

SKILLS SUMMARY

- Next.js
- Remix.js
- Gatsby.js
- Shopware
- Nuxt.js
- TypeScript
- PHP & Symfony
- Styled Components & TailwindCSS
- Figma
- Adobe Creative Cloud

PIOTR POSPIECH

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

My name is Piotr Pospiech, a frontend developer from Poland based in Aarhus, Denmark. I recently completed my Web Developer Bachelor's degree in January 2023, after finishing my Multimedia Design AP in 2021. With over 2 years of industry experience, I have worked with a diverse range of companies, including startups, digital design agencies, and big eCommerce consultancies.

I am a curious, driven and passionate individual who is always eager to learn and grow. I have great communication skills meaning I can easily adjust to different team dynamics and communication styles. I am also a supportive team player and can take initiative when necessary.

Overall, I am dedicated to my work and strive to deliver high-quality results for my clients and employers.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Geni ApS - frontend/fullstack developer

Aarhus | Sep. 2021 - Feb. 2023

- Working with complex backend solutions.
- Working with various eCommerce platforms and developing web shops.
- Communicating between design, frontend and backend team.
- Research, exploring and development of new tools based on new technologies.

IMPACT A/S - frontend engineer

Aarhus | Aug. 2022 - Jan. 2023

- Functioning within a big, diverse and international team.
- Time management and time registration
- Working with industry standard technologies
- Taking a leadership position within a project
- Research, exploring and development of new tools based on new technologies.

LANGUAGES



English - fluent, certified



Danish - moderate, still learning, DU module 4



Polish - fluent, native language

CERTIFICATES



Future Skill Talent Program 2022



Oxford English Certificate of Proficiency

Duckwise ApS - frontend developer

Aarhus | Jan. 2021 - Mar. 2021

- Managed complex projects from start to finish.
- Collaborated with other designers and developers
- Managing various size clients

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Business Academy Aarhus - Multimedia Design AP Aarhus | 2019 - 2021

- Working with all the aspects of creative process.
- Making projects and developing solutions for real clients to be implemented in the future.
- Gaining experience and more professionalism.

Business Academy Aarhus - Web development BA Aarhus | 2021 - 2023

- Working with both frontend and backend.
- Deep understanding of the complete web solutions from design theory to frontend/backend development.
- Understanding of the core concepts within web and web development
- Mobile App development and Game development

PERSONAL INFORMATION

In my free time I remain an active person I do a lot of sports like running, going to the gym, playing volleyball or football.

Besides sports I also indulge in various side activities like public speaking club Toastmasters reading books, video games or hanging out with my friends.

I would consider myself relatively open person I find myself well in a new surroundings and have a ease of establishing new relationships. I am detailed, focused and driven person that functions well in many team dynamics where I can take a different roles depending on the demand.